{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Maggie _________ be in the classroom. I saw her in the restaurant two minutes ago.",
      "a": "shouldn't",
      "b": "mustn't",
      "c": "may not",
      "d": "can't",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Can: \t used to say that something is possible\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "One ought _________ for what one hasn't done.",
      "a": "to not be punished",
      "b": "not to be punished",
      "c": "not be punished",
      "d": "to not punished",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- (Passive voice) : Ought (not) to be +PP",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It's nearly six o'clock. Tracy ___ be here at any moment.",
      "a": "need",
      "b": "shall",
      "c": "might",
      "d": "should",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n-Should: used to say that you expect something to happen or be true\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Human beings _________ die without air or water.",
      "a": "have to",
      "b": "will",
      "c": "should",
      "d": "must",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Will: used to say what always happens in a particular situation or what is generally true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Must I take a bus to your house? \"No, you ___. It's just about a 10-minute walk from here.\"",
      "a": "don't have to",
      "b": "must not",
      "c": "don't need",
      "d": "shouldn't",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Must: used in negative sentences to say that something should not happen, because of a rule or law or because of the situation",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The cleaner in the office ___ the truth.",
      "a": "didn't dare saying",
      "b": "dare not to say",
      "c": "did not dare to say",
      "d": "dare not saying",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Dare to do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ it be Jenny that took away the key?",
      "a": "Can",
      "b": "Could",
      "c": "should",
      "d": "will",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Could: used to say that something is possible or might happen",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Five months ago, I bought a motorcycle for myself. If you live in a city, it is often faster than a car and you ___ worry about parking.",
      "a": "may not",
      "b": "must not",
      "c": "don't have to",
      "d": "should not",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Have to: used to say that you are sure something will happen or something is true\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It's my birthday this Friday. Welcome to my party at night. \"Thank you. ___. Happy Birthday to You.\"",
      "a": "I will",
      "b": "I do",
      "c": "I have",
      "d": "I can",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Will\" is used to show that someone is willing or ready to do something ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will you please go to Las Vegas with us? \"No ___.\"",
      "a": "shall not",
      "b": "wouldn't",
      "c": "shouldn't",
      "d": "won't",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Would not: used to say that someone refused to do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}